<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Good Governance]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Good Governance]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 21:47:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Voluntary Associations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Voluntary Associations</h1><p>The principles that guide the organization, management and conduct of voluntary associations should be grounded in the same three foundation principles: love of all stakeholders, respect for the individual agency of all stakeholders and individual accountability.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/other-implications-of-good-governance/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dc11e344-d7cd-465c-bebc-711886984966</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 21:47:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Free Exercise of Conscience]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Free Exercise of Conscience</h1><p>Section 134 of the Doctrine and Covenants is a declaration of belief regarding governments and laws. This declaration was approved by a conference of the Church for inclusion in the 1835 edition of the Doctrine and Covenants. While the section has been included in every edition since and is often quoted by Church authorities, the minutes of the conference in which the declaration was read and approved for publication are clear that it was accepted as the “belief, or ‘opinion’ of the officers of the Church” and not as a revelation.[1] At the October, 1928 General Conference of the Church, President Heber J. Grant affirmed that Section 134 is “a declaration of the belief of our Church regarding the governments and laws, …” [2] Because of its long history as the most formal and officially accepted statement of LDS beliefs about government and law, it is also worth careful examination and comparison with the foundational principles articulated here.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/dandc-134/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1fd7e8ce-7a68-4401-8276-5790c072978b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 21:28:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Love Thy Neighbor as Thyself]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Love Thy Neighbor as Thyself</h1><p>The first foundational principle for human interaction was given by the Savior: “Thou shalt love thy neighbor as thyself.” (Matt 22:39) In 1831, the Lord reiterated this principle to a conference of early Saints using repetition and a parable to emphasize the point more strongly:</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/foundational-principles-of-good-governance/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">613fbb89-fdf1-4e0d-8ad3-ae22da878012</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 21:23:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Fundamental Principles of Good Governance in Civil Society.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Fundamental Principles of Good Governance in Civil Society.</h1><p>While the central focus is on governments, the intent here is to articulate principles that apply to any collaborative human effort and any organization. The approach taken is to ground the discussion in scripture and authoritative writings of the modern prophets to the extent possible. In doing so, there is of course the potential for “wresting” the scriptures, especially when considering the implications of the teachings in domains not directly addressed in the texts themselves. Nevertheless, a careful consideration of the principles that should underlie the governance of organizations can provide guidance for both the development and management of those organizations.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/spiritual-principles-for-secular-governance/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">10d21cab-744d-4ad7-9abb-aed1818a5b0e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 21:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Popular sovereignty—]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Popular sovereignty—</h1><p>The U.S. Constitution was divinely inspired and consequently if the foundation principles identified here are correct, they should be abundantly visible in that document. As the early Saints faced persecution in Missouri, the Prophet Joseph articulated the Lord’s views on the Constitution as he instructed the Saints to seek relief,</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/the-us-constitution/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">318715d2-d532-4c5a-bb7c-67dde6649884</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 20:47:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Good Governance?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>What is Good Governance?</h1><p>The governance of all organizations and institutions should be grounded on three principles:</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/what-is-good-governance/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a1b0b2b0-4eca-423c-82fe-46ed70699494</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 20:39:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Collective Agency]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Collective Agency</h1><p>In 1842 Joseph Smith listed as one of the articles of the LDS faith that, as a people, we believe in being subject to government officials and in “obeying, honoring and sustaining the law.” (AF 1:12) Section 134 of the Doctrine and Covenants goes further and states as a belief of the Church that “governments were instituted of God for the benefit of man; and that he holds men accountable for their acts in relation to them, both in making laws and administering them, for the good and safety of society.” (D&C 134:1)</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/collective-agency/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">24e6e848-ef27-4e4c-8fee-b2fda9ccab90</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 20:31:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Citizen Saints]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Citizen Saints</h1><p>Working conclusions about the ends and means of governments derived from the spiritual principles:</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/goodgovernance/citizen-saints/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6cd8e53b-272c-4935-9055-1da1181f1c3a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 21:41:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>